personal there you know
well this is
always refers to
Noah
the Bible says that
a raven was sent and the Raven I think
disappeared then the doubt of region was
said he just came with some leaves
always lived then he knew there was land
she need refers to Mount Sinai and
therefore to Moses and the Holy Land
referring to Mecca refers to Abraham in
jail for Muhammad
but as I said
before the Quran does not mention that
Adam blessed himself which speak leaves
the Quran does not mention that Noah
sent
a pigeons which came up with
only for branches and so on
this literally
I mean
very good man who was killed during
National
says this huh
but he does not
try to prove it he was using his
religious nutrition and a very good man
like this
has found religious equations are they
good a very good man like him so much
you sympathize the TV was killed
but Thai kutu was using a kind of area
on account of his religious inclination
and religious intrition he said the same
thing that this refers to Aidan No One
Source awesome
now we also accepted this sound between
more or less we accepted it because it
made sense
but
not only is the question
because the Bible has told us something
about it give me now we check it with
economic
alhamdulillah
in Surah 3
verse 33 now living in California
in Surah 3 verse 33 look what Allah
Allah has chosen a down okay
no one
the family of Abraham in the family of
Imran
as Messengers to all the people of
course you know that that is the key
therefore that interpretation which we
accepted that evening
is a good one because it is supported by
the Quran itself look what the Quran
said
by defeat we say feed Adam
by the only no one by Monday night Moses
Abraham song
reproducing our religious inclination
in the Quran Allah has chosen either you
see
no one this is
the olive the family of Abraham that
refers to
Ibrahim is
Imran Republic of
Moses
because Christ the mother of Christ
belongs to the family of Arun
so here I think we have we should be
convinced that when Allah says he will
explain to us he has to clue Somewhere
Only what's giving it for us to love the
Quran and you know we love it the more
it opens itself to our understanding
thus interpretation of child cultural
explanation of star Prasad I think they
are very good acceptable
not because they said so but because the
Quran okay
now
let's go into this palette okay
that same verse that same chapter 95
tonight
95.
foreign
[Music]
except those who believe and want
righteousness they will enjoy a
well-deserved pre-conference all right
this first time we created the human in
defense design
[Music]
in a state of perfect provisions
then we reverted him to the Glorious of
the lonely
this is what happens with people disobey
Allah when the Rope of his obedience is
taken away from Vietnam
obedience is taken away from me and it
becomes this religion many becomes the
loneliest of you knowledge
except those who believe and work
righteousness devotee is
good works and so on but this who are
those who believe and work righteousness
these are the people who were the road
of righteousness his magnificent and his
name is wrong
it is a road that will make them
preserve Paradise because it's a perfect
law and taught by Allah himself for us
to help and so you can now see your
brothers and sisters that Surah 95 which
begins with
Ada what is
ends up with what with the children of
Adam and Anthony in the Quran he says we
have taught the children of Adam how to
erode for righteousness
foreign
[Music]
already
um
[Music]
this is that
says I give you a and b so it's good and
yeah
I give you a and b
is not a substitute a but that b is a
qualification of Jose I give you plenty
garments
and the one of righteousness is better
better than the hips
not both of them displaying the
government
now even the leaves of paradise could be
symbolic
yeah
that's I mean like it just shows the
gross interpretation it's good that
Quran translation
then he says
he says garments is a luxury then he
says the garments of righteousness are
better however
the other government what I'm trying to
say is
not of choice
for the other one but one sentence is a
continuation of the
I will give you
intelligence
foreign
that's a problem that's in translating
from Arabic to English English language
is strong in terms
now is that prominent and perhaps here
that's not that's Arabic yes
to the Philippines
it's familiar to me
next time
the first half I mean
don't say what it is let me see if I can
find it myself
one nothing
is
linguistic analysis
yes
okay no no this is something else this
is 20 118.
is the original Club
the original clothing okay you see
2008 guarantee that you don't hunger
then they become naked see
ing
yeah
organic
foreign
[Music]
minimum requirement for salvation
and this is one of the most important
verses and bathrooms in Quran yeah two
head seven
okay
this is a very important bathroom in
Islam
because people will come to you and ask
can a Christian make it to heaven
can a Jew make it to heaven
can a person who convert it from
Christianity to Judaism Judaism to Islam
or Islam to Christianity can this person
make it to heaven
very good Quest
are the Muslims the only people who make
it to heaven
so the answer is in this book
those who believe those who are Jewish
the Christian and the cardboard
any of them who believe in God and the
last day and lead the righteous life
shall receive the recompense from the
Lord
have nothing to fear nor will they agree
so I hope you'll add this part of
dropped in the translation shall receive
the recompense from the Lord
and they have nothing to fear nor will
they agree
if you join any other religion
in the past in the future and they tell
you this these are the only people who
will go to heaven
you will take off
just plead because they are wrong
what this verse is telling us that
anybody who believes in God
the creator of Destiny verse the ruler
of this universe
and believes in the day of judgment
accountability Resurrection
and live the righteous life that person
has attained the minimum requirements of
Celebration and will go to heaven
whether he is Jewish or Christian or
Muslim or Buddhist or anything yes
they don't believe in God
no
no believe in God
[Music]
I I really believe that you know where I
was always
perfect yeah so you don't believe he
didn't believe in God
you believe that a false god
you believe in the creator of this
universe now if you believe in Jesus or
in Buddha as a God you're not believing
in God
that's right
but God God says he makes them satisfied
with their belief that is that is their
choice that will make them satisfied
with that but this statement is
regardless of anything else any person
who believes in God
and we're talking about only one thing
there is only one God and you either
believing in him or another false god
you believe in Jesus God and you firmly
believe in God and that you're not
believing in God
you are believing in a false god
and believing in God also implies
believing in God alone because if you
believe in God you will not go to
my notes creatures as God
well yeah then you don't believe in God
because when you believe in God you know
that he is much to
glorify must be glorious to have a son
you will understand you'll understand
of course you'll understand that God
does not need to reproduce himself
does not need to preserve the species
and that's reproduction and children is
a characteristic of emotion
So when you say a Son of God you don't
believe in God in the longer
yeah
right
then doctors
they went through it if they believe in
God they will do it by instinct
and if they come across it in Quran they
will have no objection to it they will
do it
yeah
what there are a few individuals who
reach the belief in God and they do the
prayers by Instinct they fall frustrate
the answer to your questions in sort of
three verse I think it's about three
let's go to that one because
this is the Quran
you have to take the whole six prophets
the whole of the Quran
okay I'll give you the reverse number
soon
thank you
okay right just Jews and Christians
okay now this is the answer to Debbie's
Quest
113. they are not all alive among the
people of the scripture that the Jews
and Christians there are those who are
righteous
there is science God's scriptures
throughout the night and they thought
prostrate see
you actually do I've met people like
that so they are doing this a lot by
Instinct however they don't have the
complete that corrects me you know it's
like
they're feeding their soul but not the
complete meal it's like you fill in your
body only
start
carbohydrates without the vitamins and
so forth you your body will grow and
will be sustained but it will be weak
that's why the next verse is important
says they believe in God in the last day
The Advocate righteousness and forbid
evil and they are eager to work
righteousness they are price now next
one is done I mean whatever good they do
will never go underwater so they'll be
rewarded for what they're doing but they
do not have the complete
recipe the complete meal you have to
come to Islam you have to do their
prayers our advantage is that we have
the whole thing described to us in
detail
as to how to develop and grow our soul
but a Christian or a Jew or a Buddhist
or a Hindu who comes to the conviction
that he believes or she believes in God
and when I say God you know what I'm
talking about
not Buddha not a monkey I'm not a cow
I'm Not Jesus
I got that just that one word if that
person believes in God they will do the
prayer instinctively
they do it they bow they prostrate they
make a good answer good and they
commemorate they meditate on God
and they ask they glorify God and they
ask God for forgiveness they repent to
only make a mistake and they are
beautiful and they go to heaven
this is this is all that is required
that's why being hanged up hung up on a
prophet
or a certain person is wrong all the
prophets want us to forget them and
worship God at all
he called me yesterday and he's writing
something and he said that
talking about the requirements and he
said one is the first one to declaration
and they said no justice
because
yeah
why the Quran itself tells us twice
that we should not let destruction among
the prophets so but what is required of
anybody is to declare that there is no
God except God
so this is a very important
and it shows the father also of
relationship
God is the most tolerable
and what is what is required some people
don't even have a religion they come to
the conviction this universe is created
by a creator
it must be worse and then God takes over
once the person makes a decision God
teaches them to do this a lot
and they may you know even do more than
we do more than the five prayers he got
the five prayers are the minimum
whenever you feel like it you should get
up and do something right
but don't they push too much even
but because of the the hunger of the
soul and because they reach the truth
they may do a lot more glorifying of God
asking forgiveness
and everything
you don't believe that Jesus the son of
God or a God or you don't believe that
Mary has any power
and we don't believe that the cow is
sacred
we believe in God so this is I'm going
to read the verse again verse 62.
those who believe
like us believe in this
those who are Jewish
the Christian and the converse
any of them who believe in God and the
last day and need the righteous life
shall receive the recompense from the
Lord and they have nothing to fear nor
will they agreed
now this
this verse makes the Hadith weapon very
uncomfortable
because the Hadith goes against this
and this will tell you that you have to
be a Muslim who believe in God and that
Muhammad is this and that in order to go
to heaven
as yours a Jew or a Christian we've got
to help regardless
because it's it's made by Satan
another question from this important but
there are some